Interviewer: Where were you born?
Joelle: I was born in North Carolina.
Interviewer: Do you have family there?
Joelle: No, not currently.
Interviewer: Where do you live now?
Joelle: Uh, now I live in New York City. Uh, I live in Soho.
Interviewer: Did you go out last weekend?
Katie: I did go out last weekend.
Interviewer: What did you do?
Katie: Um, I spent like all Saturday with some friends
just going out to different restaurants and seeing parts of the city.
Interviewer: What’s your favorite room in your house?
Maura: Probably my bedroom. I love sleeping.
Interviewer: Can you describe it?
Maura: Uh, yes, it’s got a bed, and two bedside tables, a wardrobe, and a chest of drawers.
Interviewer: What did you do yesterday evening?
Asya: Last night I had dinner with my brother in Brooklyn.
Interviewer: What time did you go to bed?
Asya: I went to bed around 1:00 a.m.
Interviewer: What did you do on New Year’s Eve last year?
Jake: Last year on New Year’s Eve, I went to a club in Las Vegas.
Interviewer: Did you have a good time?
Jake: I did not have a good time.